Contact

gmontoya910@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/gabriela-montoya-709046117 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Emergency

EMT

Languages

Spanish (Professional Working)

Gabriela Montoya

Registered Nurse, BSN,CEN at CHI St Luke's Vintage Hospital Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Emergency Nursing, Emergency Services, Nursing, Cath Lab, CEN, and ACLS, BEMT, PHTLS, TNCC, Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), NRP, BLS. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.) focused in Nursing from Grand Canyon University.

Experience

LifeSave Transport
Flight Nurse
September 2019 - Present (9 months)

CHI St. Luke's Health
Registered Nurse
November 2016 - July 2019 (2 years 9 months)
Tomball, Tx.

Emergency Services/ Cath Lab

Emerus Registered Nurse

August 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 8 months)

Tomball, Texas

Emergency Registered Nurse

Memorial Hermann Health System Perioperative Nurse November 2010 - March 2015 (4 years 5 months)

Post Anesthesia Care Unit , Recovery of post surgical patients , cardiac cath lab and Endoscopy unit patients

Harris Health System Registered Nurse September 1994 - March 2015 (20 years 7 months)

BEN TAUB TRAUMA CENTER

Level One Trauma Registered Nurse, CEN, EMT-B

Harris County Emergency Corps Flight Nurse 2009 - 2010 (1 year)

Houston, Texas Area

Emergency air transport of critically-ill patients to designated higher level of care facilities.

Education

Grand Canyon University

Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.), Nursing · (2016 - 2017)

Training Division

Certification/License , Emergency Medical Technology/Technician (EMT Basic) \cdot (2015 - 2016)